<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TrackHealth</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">open navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">close navigation Drawer</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <style name="CustomSearchViewStyle" parent="Widget.AppCompat.SearchView">
        <!-- Customize other attributes as needed -->
        <item name="android:textColor">#00695C</item>
    </style>

    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior">com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>


    <string name="date">
       "A well-rounded exercise routine should include a variety of activities. These workouts can help you improve and maintain your fitness, strength, and flexibility.

Here are 7 ideas to help you get started:

1. Walking

Walking is a low-impact activity that many people enjoy. Getting your steps can improve your blood pressure, glucose, and cholesterol levels. And 30 minutes of brisk walking –– or about 100 steps a minute –– is a great way to meet the ADA's recommendation for daily aerobic exercise.

You can also boost the intensity of your walks by adding activities like stair climbing. But if you weren't active before your diabetes diagnosis, consider starting slowly and gradually upping the pace.

2. Water aerobics

There are plenty of reasons to take your workout to the pool. Water exercises like swimming are easy on the joints and may reduce blood sugar levels. They may also boost overall fitness, strength, and heart health in people with T2D.

3. High intensity interval training

With HIIT, you switch between short bouts of high-intensity activities and longer bouts of lower-intensity moves. You can add it to various exercises like running and cycling. If you have Type 2 diabetes, HIIT may decrease your fasting blood sugar.

4. Weight training

This form of strength training uses weights or other equipment to build or maintain muscle mass and strength. And it may increase insulin sensitivity and glucose tolerance in people with T2D.

5. Yoga

Yoga involves low-impact movement, meditation, and breathing. It can improve balance, flexibility, and strength. This is especially helpful for older people with T2D who might be at greater risk of falling. The practice may also help you manage your blood sugar and cholesterol levels.

6. Tai chi

Tai chi also combines low-impact moves, meditation, and breathing techniques. The ancient practice promotes better balance, range of motion, and overall well-being. And adding it to your fitness routine may lower your blood sugar.

7. Pilates

Another low-impact form of exercise, Pilates earns a spot on this list for good reason. It uses repetitive movements and breath control to strengthen your core and improve your balance and posture. And a study showed that practicing Pilates helped participants with T2D control their blood glucose.

"
    </string>
    <string name="channel_name">Trial</string>
    <string name="channel_description">This is a trial</string>
    <string name="information1">
"Yoga is an excellent way to get sweaty and centered, whether you're a total newbie or longtime pro. Plus, there are some seriously awesome health benefits of yoga that you can score from a daily practice.

Whether you want a physically demanding yoga class, or a relaxing, meditative one, there are plenty of different yoga styles to suit a variety of skill levels and needs.

Benefits of yoga

Yoga is an excellent way to get sweaty and centered, whether you're a total newbie or longtime pro. Plus, there are some seriously awesome health benefits of yoga that you can score from a daily practice.

    yoga can improve physical health by lowering blood pressure, reducing the risk of heart disease1, and aiding digestion. It may also help practitioners sleep better and manage stress2. Research indicates the mind-body practice supports mental health, specifically; one study found regular yoga may help ease depressive symptoms.

The Major types of yoga
1.
Vinyasa yoga
Vinyasa means "to place in a special way" and, in this case, yoga postures. Vinyasa yoga is often considered the most athletic yoga style, and was adapted from ashtanga yoga in the 1980s. Many types of yoga can also be considered "vinyasa flows," such as ashtanga, power yoga, and prana.

How to practice:
In vinyasa classes, movements are coordinated with your breath in order to flow from one pose to another. Vinyasa styles can vary depending on the teacher, and there can be many types of poses in different sequences. I personally teach an alignment-based style of vinyasa and choreograph new flows every time, but I also like to hold some of the poses a bit longer after warming up. You can find more information on specific vinyasa poses and benefits here.

2.
Hatha yoga
The Sanskrit term "hatha" is an umbrella term for all physical postures of yoga. In the West, hatha yoga simply refers to all the other styles of yoga (ashtanga, Iyengar, etc.) that are grounded in a physical practice. However, there are other branches of yoga such as kriya, raja, and karma yoga that are separate from the physical-based yoga practice. The physical-based yoga is the most popular and has numerous styles.

How to practice:
Hatha yoga classes are best for beginners since they are usually paced slower than other yoga styles. Hatha classes today are a classic approach to breathing and exercises. If you are brand-new to yoga, hatha yoga is a great entry point to the practice.

3.
Iyengar yoga
Iyengar yoga was founded by B.K.S. Iyengar and focuses on alignment as well as detailed and precise movements. In an Iyengar class, students perform a variety of postures while controlling the breath.

How to practice:
Generally, poses are held for a long time while adjusting the minutiae of the pose. Iyengar relies heavily on props to help students perfect their form and go deeper into poses in a safe manner. Although you won't jump around, you will definitely get a workout and feel incredibly open and relaxed after an Iyengar class. This style is really great for people with injuries who need to work slowly and methodically.

4.
Kundalini yoga
Kundalini yoga practice is equal parts spiritual and physical. This style is all about releasing the kundalini energy in your body said to be trapped, or coiled, in the lower spine.

How to practice:
A kundalini class will really work your core and breath with fast-moving, invigorating postures and breath exercises. These classes are pretty intense and can involve chanting, mantra, and meditation. To learn more about this specific practice, check out our kundalini yoga explainer.

5.
Ashtanga yoga
In Sanskrit, ashtanga is translated as "Eight Limb path." In Mysore, India, people gather to practice this form of yoga together at their own pace—if you see Mysore-led ashtanga, it's expected of you to know the series. Vinyasa yoga stems from ashtanga as the flowing style linking breath to movement. To learn more about this specific practice, check out our beginner's guide to ashtanga yoga.

How to practice:
Ashtanga yoga involves a very physically demanding sequence of postures, so this style of yoga is definitely not for the beginner. It takes an experienced yogi to really love it. Ashtanga starts with five sun salutation A's and five sun salutation B's and then moves into a series of standing and floor postures.

6.
Bikram yoga
Bikram yoga is named after Bikram Choudhury and features a sequence of set poses in a sauna-like room—typically set to 105 degrees and 40% humidity. Choudhury faced sexual assault and harassment lawsuits in the U.S. and fled to Mexico in 2017. Many studios that were formerly Bikram now practice hot yoga, in an effort to disassociate with the founder.

How to practice:
The sequence never changes and includes a series of 26 basic postures, with each one performed twice. Many of these poses are focused on proper alignment. If you're interested in yoga with the heat turned up, look for studios that offer hot yoga classes.

7.
Yin yoga
Yin yoga is a slow-paced style of yoga with seated postures that are held for longer periods of time. Yin can also be a meditative yoga practice that helps you find inner peace.

How to practice:
Yin is a great class for beginners, as postures can be held anywhere from 45 seconds to 2 minutes. The classes are relaxed, as you're supposed to let gravity do most of the work. Check out our crash course on everything you need to know about yin yoga, found here.

8.
Restorative yoga
Restorative yoga focuses on winding down after a long day and relaxing your mind. At its core, this style focuses on body relaxation. Restorative yoga also helps to cleanse and free your mind.
    How to practice:
You'll spend more time in fewer postures throughout a restorative yoga class. Many of the poses are modified to be easier and more relaxing. Like Iyengar, many props are used and placed just right, such as blankets, bolsters, and eye pillows. All of the props are there to help you sink deeper into relaxation."
</string>
    <string name="information2">
  "Heart-healthy diet: 4 steps to prevent heart disease

      1. Control portion sizes
  How much you eat is just as important as what you eat. Overloading your plate, taking seconds and eating until you feel stuffed can lead to eating more calories than you should. Portions served in restaurants often are larger than anyone needs.

  Follow a few simple tips to control food portion size. These tips can help you shape up your diet as well as your heart and waistline:

  Use a small plate or bowl to help control your portions.
  Eat more low-calorie, nutrient-rich foods such as fruits and vegetables.
  Eat smaller amounts of high-calorie, high-sodium foods. These include refined, processed and fast foods.
 It's also important to keep track of the number of servings you eat. Keep these points in mind:

A serving size is a specific amount of food. It's defined by common measurements such as cups, ounces or pieces. For example, one serving of pasta is about 1/3 to 1/2 cup, or about the size of a fist. A serving of meat, fish or chicken is about 2 to 3 ounces. That's about the size and thickness of a deck of cards.
The recommended number of servings in a food group may vary. It depends on the specific diet or guidelines you're following.
Judging serving size is a learned skill. You may need to use measuring cups and spoons or a scale until you're comfortable with your judgment.
2. Eat more vegetables and fruits
Vegetables and fruits are good sources of vitamins and minerals. They're also low in calories and rich in fiber. Vegetables and fruits, like other plants or plant-based foods, contain substances that may help prevent heart disease. Eating more fruits and vegetables also may help you eat less higher calorie food. Some examples of high-calorie foods are meat, cheese and snack foods.

Getting more vegetables and fruits in your diet can be easy. Keep vegetables washed and cut in your refrigerator for quick snacks. Keep fruit in a bowl in your kitchen so that you'll remember to eat it. Choose recipes that have vegetables or fruits as the main ingredients. These include vegetable stir-fry dishes or fresh fruit mixed into salads.

Fruits and vegetables to choose	Fruits and vegetables to limit
Fresh or frozen vegetables and fruits.
Low-sodium canned vegetables.
Canned fruit packed in 100% juice or water.
Coconut.
Vegetables with creamy sauces.
Fried or breaded vegetables.
Canned fruit packed in heavy syrup.
Frozen fruit with sugar added.
3. Choose whole grains
Whole grains are good sources of fiber and other nutrients that play roles in heart health and controlling blood pressure. You can get more whole grains by making simple swaps with refined grain products. Or try a whole grain you haven't had before. Healthy choices include whole-grain farro, quinoa and barley. At least half of the grains you eat should be whole grains.

Grain products to choose	Grain products to limit or avoid
Whole-wheat flour.
Whole-grain bread, preferably 100% whole-wheat bread or 100% whole-grain bread.
High-fiber cereal with 5 g or more fiber in a serving.
Whole grains such as brown rice, barley and buckwheat (kasha).
Whole-grain pasta.
Oatmeal (steel-cut or regular).
White, refined flour.
White bread.
Muffins.
Frozen waffles.
Cornbread.
Doughnuts.
Biscuits.
Quick breads.
Cakes.
Pies.
Egg noodles.
Buttered popcorn.
High-fat snack crackers.
4. Limit unhealthy fats
Limit the amount of saturated and trans fats you eat. This helps lower your blood cholesterol and lower your risk of a common heart condition called coronary artery disease. A high blood cholesterol level can lead to a buildup of plaques in the arteries, called atherosclerosis. And that can raise the risk of heart attack and stroke.

The American Heart Association offers these guidelines for how much fat to include in a heart-healthy diet:

Type of fat	Recommendation
Saturated fat	Less than 6% of total daily calories. If you're eating 2,000 calories a day, that's about 11 to 13 grams.
Trans fat	Stay away from them.
Note: The 2020-2025 Dietary Guidelines for Americans recommend limiting saturated fat to less than 10% of total daily calories.

There are simple ways to cut back on saturated and trans fats for a heart-healthy diet:

Trim fat from meat or choose lean meats with less than 10% fat.
Use less butter, margarine and shortening when cooking and serving.
Use low-fat substitutions when you can. For example, top a baked potato with low-sodium salsa or low-fat yogurt rather than butter. Or use sliced whole fruit or low-sugar fruit spread on toast instead of margarine.
Check the food labels of cookies, cakes, frostings, crackers and chips. These foods are low on nutrition. And some of them — even those labeled reduced fat — may contain trans fats. Trans fats can no longer be added to foods in the United States. But they could be in products made in other countries. Trans fats may be listed as partially hydrogenated oil on the ingredient label. Also, many of the partially hydrogenated fats or trans fats typically contained in desserts and snack foods have been replaced with saturated fats. So it's still a good idea to limit those foods.

Fats to choose	Fats to limit
Olive oil.
Canola oil.
Vegetable and nut oils.
Margarine, trans fat free.
Cholesterol-lowering margarine, such as Benecol, Promise Activ or Smart Balance.
Nuts and seeds.
Avocados.
Butter.
Lard.
Bacon fat.
Gravy.
Cream sauce.
Nondairy creamers.
Hydrogenated margarine and shortening.
Cocoa butter, found in chocolate.
Coconut, palm, cottonseed and palm kernel oils.
When you use fats, choose unsaturated ones. There are two main types. Monounsaturated fats are found in products such as olive oil or canola oil. Polyunsaturated fats are found in certain fish and in avocados, nuts and seeds. When used in place of saturated fats, unsaturated fats may help lower your total blood cholesterol. But it's still important to limit how much of these fats you eat. All types of fats are high in calories.

An easy way to add healthy fat — and fiber — to your diet is to use ground flaxseed. Flaxseeds are small brown seeds that are high in fiber and healthy fats called omega-3 fatty acids. Studies have shown that flaxseed lowers unhealthy cholesterol levels in some people. You can grind flaxseeds in a coffee grinder or food processor. Then stir a teaspoon of the ground flaxseed into yogurt, applesauce or hot cereal."
</string>
    <string name="information3">
"Regular physical activity is one of the easiest ways to reduce your risk for chronic disease and to improve your quality of life. But most Americans do not move enough. No matter your age or ability, you can choose to move more for better health. And if pain, a chronic condition, or limited mobility keep you from living a more active lifestyle, a physical therapist can help you overcome barriers to physical activity.

Make physical activity a priority to:
1. Improve your memory and brain function (all age groups).
2. Protect against many chronic diseases.
3. Aid in weight management.
4. Lower blood pressure and improve heart health.
5. Improve your quality of sleep.
6. Reduce feelings of anxiety and depression.
7. Combat cancer-related fatigue.
8. Improve joint pain and stiffness.
9. Maintain muscle strength and balance.
10. Increase life span.
Physical therapists are movement experts who improve quality of life through hands-on care, patient education, and prescribed movement. Physical therapists treat people of all ages and abilities and empower you to take an active part in your care. After an evaluation, your physical therapist will design a treatment plan for your specific needs and goals.
Choose more movement. Choose better health. Choose physical therapy."
</string>
    <string name="information4">
"For heart disease patients, incorporating fitness knowledge into their daily routines is crucial for improving their health and managing their condition. Here’s a detailed guide with context on why and how certain types of physical activities can benefit heart disease patients:
  Importance of Exercise for Heart Disease Patients
    Regular physical activity helps improve cardiovascular health by:

        1.Strengthening the Heart Muscle: Exercise makes the heart more efficient at pumping blood.
        2.Lowering Blood Pressure: Regular physical activity can help reduce high blood pressure, a major risk factor for heart disease.
        3.Improving Circulation: Physical activity enhances blood flow, which can help reduce the risk of blood clots.
        4.Controlling Weight: Maintaining a healthy weight reduces the strain on the heart.
        5.Improving Cholesterol Levels: Exercise can increase HDL (good cholesterol) and lower LDL (bad cholesterol) levels.
    Recommended Types of Exercises

        1. Aerobic ExercisesBenefits: Improve cardiovascular fitness, help control weight, and lower blood pressure.
        Examples:Walking: A simple and effective way to start. Aim for brisk walking for at least 30 minutes a day.
        Swimming: A low-impact exercise that is easy on the joints and beneficial for the heart.
        Cycling: Both stationary and outdoor cycling can enhance heart health.
        2. Strength Training
        Benefits: Builds muscle mass, improves metabolism, and enhances overall physical strength.
        Examples:Light Weightlifting: Use light weights or resistance bands. Focus on all major muscle groups, aiming for two non-consecutive days per week.
        Bodyweight Exercises: Exercises like squats, lunges, and push-ups can be effective.
        3. Flexibility and Balance Exercises
        Benefits: Improve flexibility, reduce the risk of injury, and enhance overall mobility.
        Examples:
        Yoga: Incorporates stretching and balance, along with breathing exercises that can reduce stress.
        Tai Chi: A gentle form of exercise that combines slow, deliberate movements with deep breathing.
    Exercise Guidelines for Heart Disease Patients

       1. Consult a Doctor: Always check with a healthcare provider before starting a new exercise regimen.
       2. Start Slowly: Gradually increase the intensity and duration of exercise.Warm-Up and Cool Down: Begin with a 5-10 minute warm-up and end with a cool-down period to avoid sudden strain on the heart.
       3. Monitor Symptoms: Be aware of any unusual symptoms such as chest pain, dizziness, or shortness of breath, and stop exercising immediately if they occur.
       4. Stay Hydrated: Drink plenty of water before, during, and after exercise."
</string>
    <string name="information5">
"Depression and anxiety are common mental health conditions that can significantly impact an individual's quality of life. However, various strategies and practices can help manage and alleviate these conditions. Here’s a comprehensive guide on how to overcome depression and anxiety through lifestyle changes, therapeutic approaches, and self-care practices.

Understanding Depression and Anxiety
        Depression: Characterized by persistent feelings of sadness, hopelessness, and a lack of interest or pleasure in activities. It can also involve physical symptoms such as changes in appetite, sleep disturbances, and fatigue.
        Anxiety: Involves excessive worry, fear, or nervousness about everyday situations. Physical symptoms may include increased heart rate, rapid breathing, and difficulty concentrating.

Strategies to Overcome Depression and Anxiety
       1. Exercise Regularly
        Benefits: Physical activity releases endorphins, which are natural mood lifters. Exercise can also reduce symptoms of anxiety by promoting relaxation.
        Recommended Activities:
        Aerobic Exercises: Activities like walking, running, swimming, and cycling can improve mood and energy levels.
        Strength Training: Weightlifting or resistance exercises can boost self-esteem and overall physical health.
        Yoga and Tai Chi: These practices combine physical movement with mindfulness and deep breathing, reducing stress and promoting mental clarity.
      2. Adopt a Healthy Diet
        Benefits: Proper nutrition supports overall brain health and can influence mood and energy levels.
        Nutritional Tips:
        Eat Balanced Meals: Include a variety of fruits, vegetables, whole grains, lean proteins, and healthy fats.
        Avoid Excessive Sugar and Caffeine: These can lead to mood swings and exacerbate anxiety.
        Stay Hydrated: Dehydration can affect mood and energy levels.
      3. Practice Mindfulness and Meditation
        Benefits: Mindfulness and meditation help in focusing on the present moment, reducing negative thinking patterns associated with depression and anxiety.

        Techniques:
           Mindfulness Meditation: Focus on your breathing and observe your thoughts without judgment.
        Progressive Muscle Relaxation: Tense and relax different muscle groups to reduce physical tension and stress.
        Guided Imagery: Visualize calming scenes to promote relaxation and reduce anxiety.
      4. Establish a Regular Sleep Routine
         Benefits: Quality sleep is crucial for mental health. Poor sleep can worsen symptoms of depression and anxiety.
      Sleep Tips:
        Maintain a Consistent Sleep Schedule: Go to bed and wake up at the same time every day.
        Create a Relaxing Bedtime Routine: Activities like reading, taking a warm bath, or listening to calming music can prepare your body for sleep.
        Limit Screen Time Before Bed: Exposure to screens can interfere with the production of melatonin, the sleep hormone
      5. Seek Professional Help
        Benefits: Professional support from therapists or counselors can provide effective treatments and coping strategies.
    Therapeutic Approaches:
        Cognitive Behavioral Therapy (CBT): Focuses on identifying and changing negative thought patterns and behaviors.
        Dialectical Behavior Therapy (DBT): Combines cognitive-behavioral techniques with mindfulness practices.
        Medication: Antidepressants or anti-anxiety medications prescribed by a doctor can be helpful in managing symptoms.
        6. Build a Support System
        Benefits: Social support can provide emotional comfort and practical help, reducing feelings of isolation.
        Ways to Build Support:
        Connect with Friends and Family: Share your feelings and experiences with trusted loved ones.
        Join Support Groups: Participate in groups for people experiencing similar issues, either in person or online.
        Volunteer: Helping others can improve your mood and provide a sense of purpose."
</string>
    <string name="diet">
"Gaining muscle requires a combination of strength training and a nutrient-rich diet. Here are key foods to include:
        Protein-Rich Foods
        1.Lean Meats: Chicken breast, turkey, lean beef – essential for muscle repair and growth.
        2.Fish: Salmon, tuna – rich in protein and omega-3 fatty acids.
        3.Eggs: High-quality protein and nutrients.
        4.Dairy: Greek yogurt, cottage cheese, milk – contain casein and whey protein.
        5.Legumes: Lentils, chickpeas – good source of plant-based protein.
        6.Protein Supplements: Whey, casein, plant-based powders – convenient protein boost.
 Complex Carbohydrates
       1. Whole Grains: Quinoa, brown rice, oats – provide sustained energy.
       2.Starchy Vegetables: Sweet potatoes, potatoes – rich in carbohydrates.
       3.Fruits: Bananas, berries – offer vitamins, minerals, and natural sugars.
       Healthy Fats
        1.Nuts and Seeds: Almonds, walnuts – healthy fats and protein.
        2.Avocados: Monounsaturated fats and fiber.
        3.Oils: Olive oil, coconut oil – essential fats for overall health.
  Additional Foods
        1.Tofu and Tempeh: Plant-based proteins.
        2.Lean Pork: Pork loin – high in protein.
        3.Bison: Lean and nutrient-dense meat.
  Sample Muscle-Building Meal Plan
        Breakfast: Scrambled eggs, whole-grain toast, Greek yogurt with berries.
        Snack: Protein smoothie with whey protein and banana.
        Lunch: Grilled chicken, quinoa salad, fruit.
        Snack: Cottage cheese with fruit, almonds.
        Dinner: Baked salmon, sweet potato mash, broccoli.
        Snack: Mixed nuts, milk or protein shake.
   Tips for Muscle Gain
        1.Eat Sufficient Calories: Consume more calories than you burn.
        2.Stay Hydrated: Essential for muscle function.
        3.Balanced Diet: Include protein, carbs, and fats.
        4.Frequent Meals: Multiple small meals for stable energy.
        5.Post-Workout Nutrition: Protein and carbs within 30 minutes after exercise.
   By incorporating these foods and maintaining a consistent workout regimen, you can effectively build and maintain muscle mass."
    </string>
    <string name="diet1_a">
    "It is recommended that you eat lightly on your chemotherapy day. Eating small portions slowly and every few hours seem to work best. Avoid skipping meals on these days and eating fatty, greasy or spicy foods.

What do I eat before going to chemotherapy?
Light, bland foods seem to work best. Some examples of choices are:

Plain or Fruited yogurt
Fresh fruit and cottage cheese
Poached egg and toast
Toasted bagel with a small amount of peanut butter
Cereal and milk (try Lactaid® milk, or Soy milk, if lactose intolerant)
Chicken rice soup with saltine crackers
During chemotherapy take a small, bland snack with you. You can try the above foods as well as snack on low acid juices (apple, grape, and fruit nectars), liquid yogurts, fruits such as bananas, and crackers. Bring a water bottle and fill it with your favorite beverage (avoid acidic foods which may be irritating to your digestive tract).

Juices and supplements as Ensure or Boost are usually available where you are receiving chemotherapy;
however ask in advance if these and any other foods are available. If you don’t feel like eating during the
infusion that is ok, but remember that you may feel better with eating small amounts of bland food and liquids.

Drink small amounts every ½ hour as tolerated.

What do I eat after chemotherapy and for the next few days?
Eat small meals and snacks throughout the day (aim for 5-6 smaller meals rather than 3 large meals).
Eat lower fat, blander foods!
Try colder or cool foods – these give off less odor and aroma and are especially important if you feel nauseous. Hot foods can have a more pronounced odor, therefore causing an aversion to certain foods.
Drink fluids frequently—this will prevent dehydration and remove some of the byproducts of the chemotherapy. Water is the best, but there are other sources of fluids such as:
Apple and grape juice
Fruit nectars
Low-salt broth
Clear soups
Gatorade
Popsicles and sherbert
Gelatin
Herbal teas, such as ginger and mint
Weak black teas
Take your anti-nausea medication as prescribed by your medical team."
    </string>
    <string name="diet2_b">
"What is diabetes?
If you have diabetes, your blood glucose, or blood sugar, levels are too high. Glucose comes from foods you eat. The cells of your body need glucose for energy. A hormone called insulin helps the glucose get into your cells.
  What's the best diet for diabetes?
There isn't a specific diet or meal plan that works for everybody. Your health care provider may have you see a registered dietician (RD) or a diabetes educator who can help design the best eating plan for you. The plan will consider:

Any medicines that you take
Your weight
Any other health conditions you have
Your lifestyle and tastes
Your goals
All eating plans for diabetes have a few things in common, including eating the right foods in the right amounts at the right times.

What foods should I eat if I have diabetes?
Eating the right foods for diabetes means eating a variety of healthy foods from all the food groups:

Fruits and vegetables
Whole grains, such as whole wheat, brown rice, barley, quinoa, and oats
Proteins, such as lean meats, chicken, turkey, fish, eggs, nuts, beans, lentils, and tofu
Nonfat or low-fat dairy, such as milk, yogurt, and cheese
What foods should I limit to control my blood glucose?
To keep your blood glucose under control, you may need to cut back on certain foods and drinks. This doesn't mean that you can never enjoy them. But you will need to have them less often or in smaller amounts.

High-carb foods and drinks, such as:
Sugary foods, such as candy, cookies, cake, ice cream, sweetened cereals, and canned fruits with added sugar
Drinks with added sugars, such as juice, regular soda, and regular sports or energy drinks
White rice, tortillas, breads and pasta - especially those made with white flour
Starchy vegetables, such as white potatoes, corn, and peas
Fried foods and other foods high in saturated trans fats.
Foods high in sodium (salt).
Alcohol. If you do drink, you should drink moderately. This means no more than one standard drink a day if you're a woman or two standard drinks a day if you're a man.      "
    </string>
    <string name="diet3_c">

    </string>
    <string name="diet4_d">

    </string>
</resources>